[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "669d0acf45eeb68d5d1c4eb5"
  },
  "question": "Вопрос 1",
  "answer": "Ответ 1",
  "trap_1": "Неверный 1",
  "trap_2": "Неверный 2"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "669d0acf45eeb68d5d1c4eb6"
  },
  "question": "Вопрос 2",
  "answer": "Ответ 2",
  "trap_1": "Неверный 1",
  "trap_2": "Неверный 2"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "669d0acf45eeb68d5d1c4eb7"
  },
  "question": "Вопрос 3",
  "answer": "Ответ 3",
  "trap_1": "Неверный 1",
  "trap_2": "Неверный 2"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "669d0acf45eeb68d5d1c4eb8"
  },
  "question": "Вопрос 4",
  "answer": "Ответ 4",
  "trap_1": "Неверный 1",
  "trap_2": "Неверный 2"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "669d0acf45eeb68d5d1c4eb9"
  },
  "question": "Вопрос 5",
  "answer": "Ответ 5",
  "trap_1": "Неверный 1",
  "trap_2": "Неверный 2"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "669d0acf45eeb68d5d1c4eba"
  },
  "question": "Вопрос 6",
  "answer": "Ответ 6",
  "trap_1": "Неверный 1",
  "trap_2": "Неверный 2"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "669d0acf45eeb68d5d1c4ebb"
  },
  "question": "Вопрос 7",
  "answer": "Ответ 7",
  "trap_1": "Неверный 1",
  "trap_2": "Неверный 2"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "669d0acf45eeb68d5d1c4ebc"
  },
  "question": "Вопрос 8",
  "answer": "Ответ 8",
  "trap_1": "Неверный 1",
  "trap_2": "Неверный 2"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "669d0acf45eeb68d5d1c4ebd"
  },
  "question": "Вопрос 9",
  "answer": "Ответ 9",
  "trap_1": "Неверный 1",
  "trap_2": "Неверный 2"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "669d0acf45eeb68d5d1c4ebe"
  },
  "question": "Вопрос 10",
  "answer": "Ответ 10",
  "trap_1": "Неверный 1",
  "trap_2": "Неверный 2"
}]